telugubulletin.com 2019-12-30

# Telugubulletin.com | Privacy Policy

This page informs you of www.TeluguBulletin.com and all of its sub-domains policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.

We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

 **Information Collection And Use**

While using our Website or to advertise with us, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name (“Personal Information”).

 **Log Data and Communications**

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”).

This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

In addition, we may use third party services/plugins such as Google Analytics, Vuukle etc. that collect, monitor and analyze the information

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information

 **Cookies**

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.

Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.

 **Security**

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

 **Links to Other Sites**

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by our website. It does not apply to third party website links or advertisements or content which appear on our websites and we suggest you read the privacy statements of such websites. Please be aware that we not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

 **Third-Party Advertising**

We may use third party advertising companies (like Google adsense) to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use cookies or web beacons to collect Personal or non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you.

 **Changes To This Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of January 1st 2019 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

 **Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
